Inventory of the Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace. Domestic Studies Program working papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- 1986
  - Why Is there Tenure?, Takatoshi Ito/Charles Kahn, 1986 (Box 15)
- 1987
  - Strategic Incentive Manipulation in Rivalrous Agency, Chaim Fershtman/Kenneth L. Judd, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Administrative Procedures as Instruments of Political Control, Mathew D. McCubbins/Roger G. Noll/Barry R. Weingast, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Aging, Moving, and Housing Wealth, Steven F. Venti/David A. Wise, 1987 (Box 19)
  - "Arbitrage Costs and the Efficiency of the Dollar-Sterling Gold Standard1899 1908: An Econometric Perspective", Pablo T. Spiller/Robert O. Wood, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Buyers and Entry Barriers, David T. Scheffman/Pablo T. Spiller, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Capital Gains Taxation by Realization in Dynamic General Equilibrium, Kenneth L. Judd, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Commitment in Procurement Contracting, Michael H. Riordan/David E. M. Sappington, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Compatibility Standards and the Market for Telecommunications Service, Stanley M. Besen/Garth Saloner, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Competition, Relativism, and Market Choice, Debra J. Aron/Edward P. Lazear, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Cooperation through Delegation, Chaim Fershtman/Kenneth L. Judd/Ehud Kalai, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Coordination through Committees and Markets, Joseph Farrell/Garth Saloner, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Cyclical Behavior of Strategic Inventories, Julio J. Rotemberg/Garth Saloner, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Debt and Distortionary Taxation in a Simple Perfect Foresight Model, Kenneth L. Judd, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Do Deficits Affect the Level of Insurance?, Gertrud M. Fremling, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Earnings Uncertainty and Intergenerational Transfers, Eytan Sheshinski, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Easy Animal Economics, Sherwin Rosen, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Economic Costs of Alzheimer's Disease, Joel W. Hay/Richard L. Ernst, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Economics, Politics, and Government Research and Development, Roger G. Noll/Linda R. Cohen, 1987 (Box 19)
  - Education, Democracy, and the Cost of Government Wealth Transfers, John R. Lott, Jr., 1987 (Box 18)
  - Effect of Rent Maximizing Unions on Why Workers Join Unions, Stephen G. Bronars/John R. Lott, Jr., 1987 (Box 17)
  - Effects of Capital Gains Taxation on Life-Cycle Investment and Portfolio Management, Yves Balcer/Kenneth L. Judd, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Empirical Study of an Auction with Asymmetric Information, Kenneth Hendricks/Robert H. Porter, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Equilibrium Political Budget Cycles, Kenneth Rogoff, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Estimating Integrated Higher Order Continuous Time Autoregressions with an Application to Money-Income Causality, A. C. Harvey/ James H. Stock, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Estimation of Dynamic Investment Function in Oil Exploration, Kenneth Hendricks/Alfonso Novales, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Existence of Nash Equilibria in Reaction Functions for Dynamic Models of Oligopoly, Arthur J. Robson, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Have IRAS Increased U.S. Savings? Evidence from Consumer expenditure Surveys, Steven F. Venti/David A. Wise, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Hierarchical Control and Investment Incentives in Procurement, Michael H. Riordan, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Hysteresis and the Evolution of Postwar U.S. and U.K. Unemployment, James H. Stock, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Industry Structure with Sequential Technology Choice, Richard P. McLean/Michael H. Riordan, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Inference in Linear Time Series Models / with some Unit Roots, Christopher A. Sims/James H. Stock/Mark W. Watson, 1987 (Box 17)
  - International Risk and Exchange Rate Overshooting, Juergen Schroeder, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Interpreting New Evidence about China and U.S. Silver Purchases, Loren Brandt/Thomas J. Sargent, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Inventories and the Propagation of Sectorial Shocks, Russell Cooper/John Haltiwanger, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Job Security and Unemployment, Edward P. Lazear, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Lump-sum payments, Edward P. Lazear, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Money and the Stock Market, Milton Friedman, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Movements Toward Free Trade and Domestic Market Performance with Imperfect Competition, Thomas W. Ross, 1987 (Box 18)
  - On Governing Multilateral Transactions with Bilateral Contracts, Jacques Cremer/Michael H. Riordan, 1987 (Box 16)
  - On the Correlation between Quits and Output, Charles M. Kahn, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Optimality of (s,S) Pricing Policies, Andrew Caplin/Eytan Sheshinski, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Predation, Monopolization, and Antitrust, Janusz A. Ordover/Garth Saloner, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Reputation, Coordination, and Monetary Policy, Kenneth Rogoff, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Reputations in the Adoption of New Technology, Kenneth Hendricks, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Selection Criteria in Coordination Games: Some Experimental Results, Russell Cooper/Douglas V. DeJong/Robert Forsythe/Thomas W. Ross, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Separating and Pooling Equilibrium in Optimal Employment Contracts, Charles M. Kahn, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Shirking and Sorting in a Political Market with Finite-Lived Politicians, John R. Lott, Jr./W. Robert Reed, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Simple Model of Optimum Life- Cycle Consumption With Earnings Uncertainty, Eytan Sheshinski, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Some Economics of Teaching, Sherwin Rosen, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Strategic Renegotiation and Contractual Simplicity, Gur Huberman/Charles M. Kahn, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Structure and Short-Run Adaptability of Labor Markets in Japan and the United States, Masanori Hashimoto/John Raisin, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Testing for Common Trends, James H. Stock/Mark W. Watson, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Time Preference, Reinforcement, and the Pattern of Payments, Edward P. Lazear, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Value of Changes in Life Expectancy, Sherwin Rosen, 1987 (Box 18)
  - War of Attrition in Continuous Time with Complete Information, Kenneth Hendricks/Andrew Weiss/Charles Wilson, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Was It Real? The Exchange Rate-Interest Differential Relation over the Modern Floating Rate Period, Richard Meese/Kenneth Rogoff, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Wealth and Poverty of Widows: Assets before and after the Husband's Death, Michael Hurd/David A. Wise, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Why Comply: Enforcing the Minimum Wage and Other Price Control Laws, John R. Lott, Jr./Russell D. Roberts, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Why is Education Publicly Provided?: A Critical Survey, John R. Lott, Jr., 1987 (Box 18)
- 1988
  - Adjusting to an Aging Labor Force, Edward P. Lazear, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Analysis and Reform of the Colombian Tax System, Charles E. McLure, Jr., 1988 (Box 19)
  - Are Congressional Committees Composed of Preference Outliers?, Keith Krehbiel, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Asymmetric Information the Timing of Payments and the Selection of Cases for Litigation, Bruce H. Kobayashi/John R. Lott, Jr., 1988 (Box 19)
  - Bargaining in Legislatures, David P. Baron/John A. Ferejohn, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Canada's New Competition Policy, Christopher J. Maule and Thomas W. Ross, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Collective Choice without Procedural Commitment, Thomas W. Gilligan and Keith Krehbiel, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Collective Choice Without Procedural Commitment, Thomas W. Gillian/William J. Marshal/Keith Krehbiel, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Constitutions and Commitment: The Evolution of Institutions Governing Public Choice in 17th Century England, Douglass C. North/Barry R. Weingast, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Decentralization, Duplication and Delay, Patrick Bolton and Joseph Farrell, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Dyadic Power, Expectations, and War, Bruce Bueno de Mesquita/David Lalman, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Econometric Issues in Modeling the Costs of AIDS, Joel W. Hay, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Empirical Foundations of the Arbitrage Pricing Theory, Bruce N. Lehmann/David M. Modest, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Equilibrium Interpretations of Employment and Real Wage Fluctuations, John Kennan, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Equilibrium Interpretations of Employment and Real Wage Fluctuations, John Kennan, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Evolution of Budget Decisionmaking and the Emergence of Federal Deficits, John Cogan, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Evolution of Congressional Budget Decision-making and the Emergence of Federal Deficits, John F. Cogan, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Exchangeability and the Structure of the Economy: A preliminary Process Analysis, John J. McCall, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Experimental Analysis of Bargaining and Strikes with One-Sided Private Information, Robert Forsythe/John Kennan/Barry Sopher, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Fads Martingales and Market Efficiency, Bruce N. Lehmann, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Firm and Worker Loyalty, Jonathan Eaton, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Fiscal Policy and Equity in Developing Countries, Charles E. McLure, Jr., 1988 (Box 19)
  - Floor Behavior in Congress: Committee Power Under the Open Rule, Barry R. Weingast, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Geometric Content Analysis Method, Allen Francis Ketcham, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Government Debt, Redistributive Fiscal policies, and the Interaction between Borrowing Constraints and Intergenerational Altruism, David Altig and Steve J. Davis, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Intertemporal Price Competition, Jonathan Eaton and Maxim Engers, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Introduction to Exchangeability and Its Economic Application, John J. McCall, 1988 (Box 2)
  - John Maynard Keynes, Milton Friedman, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Lessons for LDCs of U.S. Income Tax Reform, Charles E. McLure, Jr., 1988 (Box 19)
  - Male/Female Wage Differentials in Job Ladders, Edward P. Lazear and Sherwin Rosen, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Malthus and the Evolution of the Welfare State: An Essay on the Second Invisible Hand, Mikhail S. Bernstam, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Malthus and the Evolution of the Welfare State: An Essay on the Second Invisible Hand, Mikhail S. Bernstam, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Marginals Never Vanished?, Stephen Ansolabehere/David Brady/Morris Fiorina, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Model of Judicial Influence on Congressional Policymaking: Grove City College V. Bell, Brian A. Marks, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Monopoly Wealth and International Debt, Jonathan Eaton, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Multiplicity of Equilibria and Fluctuations in an Imperfectly Competitive Economy with Entry and Exit, Satyajit Chatterjee and Russell Cooper, 1988 (Box 1)
  - National Identity in a Divided Nation: The New Historical Museum in West Berlin, Peter Paret, 1988 (Box 20)
  - On the Relative Efficiency of Cash Transfers and Subsidies, Thomas W. Ross, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Optimal Contracts with Lock-In, Joseph Farrell and Carl Shapiro, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Organization of Informative Committees by a Rational Legislature, Thomas W. Gillian/William J. Marshal/Keith Krehbiel, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Pension Inducement to Retire: An Option Value Analysis, James H. Stock/David A. Wise, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Pension Inducement to Retire: An Option Value Analysis, James H. Stock and David A. Wise, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Pensions, The Option Value of Work and Retirement, James H. Stock/David A. Wise, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Pensions, the Option Value of Work, and Retirement, James H. Stock and David A. Wise, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Politicians, Interest Groups, and Regulators: A Multiple-Principals Agency Theory of Regulation (Or Let Them Be Bribed), Pablo T. Spiller, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Power to Propose, David P. Baron/John A. Ferejohn, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Qualitative Information, Reputation, and Monopolistic Competition, Michael R. Darby/John R. Lott, Jr., 1988 (Box 19)
  - Raising an Army: A Positive Theory of Military Recruitment, Thomas W. Ross, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Road to War is Strewn with PeacefulIntentions, Bruce Bueno de Mesquita/David Lalman, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Schumpeter and His Critics on the Future of Capitalism, Anne Wortham, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Short-Run Supply with Capacity Constraints, Valerie Y. Suslow and Timothy F. Bresnahan, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Simultaneous Equations Bias in Disaggregated Econometric Models, John Kennan, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Sophisticated voting in Congress: A Reconsideration, Keith Krehbiel and Douglas Rivers, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Stability in International Cartels: An Empirical Survey, Valerie Y. Suslow, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Stock Options and Deferred Compensation, Matthew Jackson/Edward Lazear, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Strategic Bargaining Models and Interpretation of Strike Data, John Kennan and Robert Wilson, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Subsidies to Private Spending on Public Goods, Russell Roberts, 1988 (Box 1)
  - The "Plucking Model" of Business Fluctuations Revisited, Milton Friedman, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Theory of Managed Trade, Kyle Bagwell and Robert W. Staiger, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Theory of Political Control and Agency Discretion, Randall L. Calvert/Mathew D. McCubbins/Barry R. Weingast, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Theory of the Ethnically Homogeneous Middleman Group: Beyond Markets and Hierarchies, Janet T. Landa, 1988 (Box 19)
  - U.S. Tax Laws and Capital Flight from Latin America, Charles E. McLure, Jr., 1988 (Box 1)
  - Uncertainty and the Choice of Trade Policy in Oligopolistic Industries, Russell Cooper/Raymond Riezman, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Warranties without Commitment to Market Participation, John Bigelow/Russell Cooper/Thomas W. Ross, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Why Does the Information Matrix Test Reject Too Often? A Diagnosis of Some Monte Carlo Symptoms, John Kennan/George R. Neumann, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Why Short-Lagged Relationships are More Easily Identified, Gertrud M. Fremling and John R. Lott, Jr., 1988 (Box 1)
- 1989
  - Adverse Selection in Credit Markets and Infant Industry Protection, Harry Flam and Robert W. Staiger, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Altruism, Borrowing Constraints, and Social Security, David Altig and Steve J. Davis, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Apartheid: Past, Present, and Future, Lewis H. Gann, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Asset Ownership and Market Structure in Oligopoly, Joseph Farrell and Carl Shapiro, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Bimetallism Revisited, Milton Friedman, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Cheap Talk with Two Audiences, Joseph Farrell and Robert Gibbons, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Research Through Research Joint Ventures, Neil Gandal and Suzanne Scotchmer, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Crime of 1873, Milton Friedman, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Do Business and Economic Historians Understand Corporations?, Robert Hessen, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Domestic Opposition and Foreign War, Bruce Bueno de Mesquita/David Lalman, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Dynamic Model of International Transfers of Technology, Maria Eugenia Muniagurria, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Economic Approaches to the Psychology of Organizations, Edward P. Lazear, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Fighting Fire with Fire: Amending Activity and Institutional Change in the Post-Reform Congress, Barry R. Weingast, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Gross Job Creation, Gross Job Destruction and Employment Reallocation, Steve J. Davis and John Haltiwanger, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Horizontal Mergers: An Equilibrium Analysis, Joseph Farrell and Carl Shapiro, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Measures of Welfare Dependency: An Evaluation, Thomas MaCurdy, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Mobility and Redistribution, Dennis Epple and Thomas Romer, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Model of Growth with Technology Adoption, Maria Eugenia Muniagurria, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Money and Bond Markets in France: Segmentation vs. Integration, Bernard Dumas and Bertrand Jacquillat, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Money as a Medium of Exchange in an Economy with Artificially Intelligent Agents, Ramon Marimon, Ellen McGrattan and Thomas J. Sargent, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Monotonicity in Games that Exhaust Gains to Scale, Suzanne Scotchmer and Myrna Holtz Wooders, 1989 (Box 3)
  - New Institutional Economics and the Process of Economic Development, Johan Myhrman, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Novelty and Disclosure in Patent Law, Suzanne Scotchmer and Jerry Green, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Peer Pressure and Partnerships, Eugene Kandel and Edward P. Lazear, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Pensions and Deferred Benefits as Strategic Compensation, Edward P. Lazear, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Penultimate Power: Conference Committees and the Legislative Process, Kenneth A. Shepsle/Barry R. Weingast, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Performance of Currency Portfolios Chosen by a Bayesian Technique: 1967-1985, Bernard Dumas and Bertrand Jacquillat, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Perspective on Renegotiation in Repeated Games, Dilip Abreu and David Pearce, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Political Control of Bureaucracies under Asymmetric Information, Jeffrey S. Banks/Barry R. Weingast, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Political Economy and Macroeconomics: Four Working Papers, Alberto Alesina/Alex Cukierman/Andrew Atkeson/V. V. Chari /Patrick J. Kehoe/Guido Tabellini, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Political Institutions of Representative Government: Legislatures, Barry R. Weingast, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Price and Quality in a New Product Monopoly, Kenneth L. Judd and Michael H. Riordan, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Pride of Place: The Origins of German Hegemony, Bruce Bueno de Mesquita, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Projecting the Medical Cost of HIV/AIDS: An Update with Focus on Political Epidemiology, Joel W. Hay, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Redistribution by Local Governments in a Monocentric Urban Area, Glenn Cassidy/Dennis Epple/Thomas Romer, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Sacrifice and stigma Reducing Free-Riding in Cults, Communes, and other Collectives, Laurence R. Iannaccone, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Standardization and Intellectual Property, Joseph Farrell, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Strategic Use of Antidumping Law to Enforce Tacit International Collusion, Robert W. Staiger and Frank A. Wolak, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Structure and Process; Politics and Policy: Administrative Arrangements and the Political Control of Agencies, Mathew D. McCubbins/Roger G. Noll/Barry R. Weingast, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Synthesis of the Behavioral Aspects of Welfare Dependency and an Assessment of the Findings, Thomas MaCurdy, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Technological Licensing and the Novelty Requirement in Patent Law, Jerry Green and Suzanne Scotchmer, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Timing of Intergenerational Transfers, Tax policy, and Aggregate Savings, David Altig and Steve J. Davis, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Tontines, Public Finance, and Revolution in France and Britain, 1688-1789, David R. Weir, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Uses and Abuses of Budget Baselines, Timothy J. Muris, 1989 (Box 20)
  - USSR Foreign Policy, A New Era, Richard F. Staar, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Wage Structure with Moral Hazard in Job Search, Kit-Chun Lam, Pak-Wai Liu, and Richard Yur-Chim Wong, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Writing Scripts for the Floor: Restrictive Rules in the Post-Reform House, Barry R. Weingast, 1989 (Box 10)
- 1990
  - How to Vote Whether to Vote: Decisions About Voting and Abstaining on Congressional Roll Calls, Linda R. Cohen/Roger G. Noll, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Alternative Approaches to Analyzing Economic Data, Milton Friedman and Anna J. Schwartz, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Assessing Empirical Approaches for Analyzing Taxes and Labor Supply, Thomas MaCurdy, David Green and Harry Paarsch, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Bootstrapping HIV/AIDS Projection Models: Back Calculation with Linear Inequality-Constrained Regression, Joel W. Hay and Frank A. Wolak, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Collusive Pricing with Capacity Constraints in the Presence of Demand Uncertainty, Robert W. Staiger and Frank A. Wolak, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Determinates of Vertical Integration: An Empirical Test, Marvin B. Lieberman, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Domestic Discretionary Spending in the 1980's, John F. Cogan and Timothy J. Muris, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Econometric Implications of Incentive-Compatible Regulation, Jonathan S. Feinstein and Frank A. Wolak, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Economic Effects of Expected Monetary and Fiscal Policy in Small Open Economies-An Intertemporal Approach, Juergen Schroeder and Gerhard Ruebel, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Economic Incidence of the Interstate Commerce Act of 1887: A Theoretical and Empirical Analysis of the Shorthaul Pricing Constraint, Thomas W. Gilligan/William J. Marshal/Barry R. Weingast, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Economics of Internal Labor Markets, Michael L. Wachter and Randall D. Wright, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Effect of Domestic Antidumping Law in the Presence of Foreign Monopoly, Robert W. Staiger and Frank A. Wolak, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Exit from Declining Industries: "Shakeout" or "Stakeout"?, Marvin B. Lieberman, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Financing Education in the Philippines and Its Implications on Planning and Reform, Adriano A. Arcelo, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Imperfect Competition and Basing-Point Pricing: An Application to the Softwood Plywood Industry, Thomas W. Gilligan, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Indexation and Contract Length in Unionized U.S. Manufacturing, Mark Bils, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Information and Timing in Repeated Partnerships, Dilip Abreu, Paul Milgrom and David Pearce, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Job as a Concept, Edward P. Lazear, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Merchant Gild as a Nexus of Contracts, Avner Greig, Paul Milgrom and Barry Weingast, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Performance of an Institutionalized Legislature, Thomas W. Gilligan, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Political Foundations of the Thrift Debacle, Thomas Romer and Barry R. Weingast, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Positive and Normative Models of Due Process: An Integrative Approach to Administrative Procedures, Mathew D. McCubbins/Roger G. Noll/Barry R. Weingast, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Role of Institutions in the Revival of Trade: Law Merchant, Private Judges, and the Champagne Pairs, Paul R. Milgrom/Douglass C. North/Barry R. Weingast, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Selling versus Producing in Market Fluctuations, Mark Bils, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Senate Confirmation of Supreme Court Nominations from Washington to Reagan, Peter H. Lemieux/Charles H. Stewart, III, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Sensitivity of Strategic and Corrective R&D Policy in Battles for Monopoly, Kyle Bagwell and Robert W. Staiger, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Sensitivity of Strategic and Corrective R&D Policy in Oligopolistic Industries, Kyle Bagwell and Robert W. Staiger, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Unemployment Compensation and Episodes of Nonemployment, R. Mark Gritz and Thomas MaCurdy, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Virtual Implementation in Nash Equilibium, Dilip Abreu and Arunava Sen, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Wage and Employment Patterns in Long-Term Contracts when Labor is Quasi-Fixed, Mark Bils, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Wealth of Nations and the Environment, Mikhail S. Bernstam, 1990 (Box 4)
  - When Do Power Transitions Lead to War?, Woosang Kim/James D. Morrow, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Why is Automobile Insurance in Philadelphia So Damn Expensive?, Eric Smith and Randall Wright, 1990 (Box 4)
- 1991
  - Approach to Equilibrium Selection, Akihiko Matsui and Kiminori Matsuyama, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Business, Health Care Costs and Competition, Rita Ricardo-Campbell, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Competitive Limit Pricing under Imperfect Information, Kyle Bagwell, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Conspicuous Consumption, Pure Profits, and the Luxury Tax: Some Surprising Consequences of Perfect Competition, Laurie Simon Bagwell and B. Douglas Bernheim, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Debt, Asymmetric Information, and Bankruptcy, James A. Kahn, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Island of Stone Money, Milton Friedman, 1991 (Box 5)
  - List Policies and Bait-and-Switch Strategies, Edward P. Lazear, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Monetary Value of Conscription, John R. Oneal, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Positive Theory of Statutory Interpretation, John A. Ferejohn and Barry R. Weingast, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Prices and Wages in Transition Economies, Edward P. Lazear, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Pricing to Signal Product Line Quality, Kyle Bagwell, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Quasi Process Free Valuation Model of Floating Rate Instruments, Bertrand Jacquillat and Sylvie de Laguiche, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Socialist Market Economy-Can It Work?, Rudolf Richter, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Two Americas, Two Value Systems: Blacks and Whites, Seymour Martin Lipset, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Virtual Implementation in Iteratively Undominated Strategies: Complete Information, Dilip Abreu and Hitoshi Matsushima, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Virtual Implementation in Iteratively Undominated Strategies: Complete Information, Dilip Abreu and Hitoshi Matsushima, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Why is Production More Volatile than Sales? Theory and Evidence on the Stockout-Avoidance Motive for Inventory Holding, James A. Kahn, 1991 (Box 5)
- 1992
  - Agricultural Productivity, Comparative Advantage, and Economic Growth, Kiminori Matsuyama, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Case for Monetary Competition in the Transition from Plan to Market, Annelise Anderson, 1992 (Box 6)